

MITHUN DEWRI

Data Entry & Data Analyst Professional

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

Data-driven tasks & analysis is my line of expertise. An enthusiastic technical knowledge seeker, inquisitive minded self-starter with strong logical sense, analytical ability, leadership, and communication skills who never fears to start from the beginning, has a passion for winning and loves to work under pressure

CORE COMPETENCIES

- MS Office
- Data Entry
- Conditional Formating
- Mathematical Problem Solving
- Vlookup & Hlookup
- Dropdown List
- Data Analysis
- Data Validation
- Data Presentation & Chart
- IBM SPSS
- Python (Basic)
- System customization

REACH ME AT:

Cell:

+8801717019888

Email:

mithundewri@gmail.com

LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mithun-dewri-23333520a

Address:

10/172, West NabiNagor, Kamrangirchor, Dhaka- 1211

REFERENCES

Chintu Bala

Project Co-Ordinator

BRAC

Email:sintubaladu3885@gmail.com Mob- 01517839248

PROFESSIONAL HISTORY

Data-Entry Operator & Case docket Writer (Contractual)

Shah-Ali Police Station, DMP | Nov 2020 - Present

Working remotely as a Contractual Data-Entry Operator and Police case docket writer.

Data-Entry Operator

IUCN Bangladesh | Feb 2017 - May 2019

Analyzing collected data from source documents within time limits. Compiling data, verifying the accuracy, and sorting information to prepare source data for computer entry. Reviewing data for deficiencies or errors, correcting any incompatibilities, and checking the output. Keep information confidential.

Assistant Teacher (Part-time)

West End High School | May 2015 - May 2016

Teaching as classroom assistants, supporting teachers by helping supervised activities in the classroom, working with children on an individual, small group, or whole class basis. Some assistantship work on teaching on a one-to-one basis with children with special educational needs.

ACADEMIC BACKGROUND

University Of Dhaka

Bachelor of Arts | Jun 2007 - Dec 2012 Sanscrit GPA: 3.06

CERTIFICATIONS & TRAINING

- Ms Office & Internet Browsing
- Web Design (Udemy)
- Digital Marketing
- Python(Running)
- Certificate of Acknowledgement, BADHON, (Voluntary Blood Donor's Organisation)

LANGUAGE PROFICENCY

English & Bengali

Animesh Chandra Mondol

Web Developer

LYNKTO

Email:ancientcharbak@gmail.com Mob- 01723664797

PORTFOLIO: https://drive.google.com/drive/folders/1udBwLcK YHLojTkH6xuCy6N6vr4CydWv? usp=sharing